

# RONEN KONFORTES

Senior Software Engineer +972546825502

#### o DETAILS o

+972546825502 konfortes@gmail.com

o LINKS o

Github

#### o SKILLS o

Node.Js

Golang

Ruby on Rails

Javascript

Typescript

AWS

Postgresql

Redis

C#.NET

Git

Scrum

#### ○ HOBBIES ○

Triathlon, Music, Bio-Hacking

## ○ LANGUAGES ○

Hebrew

English

## PROFILE

Software engineer with over 9 years of web development experience. Highly skilled with Ruby on Rails, Golang, Node.Js, Typescript, Javascript, .NET, AWS, Postgresql, MySql, Redis. Problems solver, team player, looking for a challenging and interesting position, developing or (preferably) building from scratch meaningful products together with great people.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## Senior Backend Engineer at First DAG, Tel-Aviv

August 2018 - March 2019

Building from scratch and end to end responsibility of First's Blockchain and crypto currencies solutions and infrastructures.

Node.Js, Typescript, Golang, Postgresql, AWS, React.

## Senior Backend Engineer at Gett, Tel-Aviv

February 2015 - June 2018

End to end responsibility of Gett's high scale on-demand services.

Building from scratch the company's Carpool system.

Ruby on Rails, Golang, Postgersql, MySql, Redis, Rabbit MQ, AWS, Firebase, Javascript, React, Vue.JS.

## Fullstack Engineer at Schneider Electric, Tel-Aviv

June 2012 - January 2015

Development and maintenance of the company's SaaS product for managing and analyzing Energy consumption. .NET, C#, SQL Server, ExtJS, Azure.

## Backend Engineer at IFN solutions, Kfar-Saba

April 2010 - April 2012

Development and maintenance of the company's ECM and BPM products. .Net, C#, Oracle DB, SQL Server, WPF, Silverlight.

#### EDUCATION

# The Academic College of Tel Aviv-Yaffo, Tel-Aviv

October 2008 - May 2012

Degree: B.s.c

Advanced courses in Mathematics, Programming, Architecture, Databases, Operating systems, etc.